

Artemii Nozdrenko

Front-End developer

Russia, Moscow

Contacts













About me

Front-End developer with experience in creating SPA using JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-Toolkit, Typescript, HTML, CSS. I'm always looking forward to improve my expertise. Usually I spend my leisure time on Codewars or reading professional literature.

Education

IT-Incubator, 2021 - 2022: Front-End developer (React + Redux, TypeScript)

The Course of Yuriy Bura, 2021 Professional development React + Redux

VGETC 2017 Technician

Language

English: Pre-Intermediate(in progress)

Russia: native

Experience

Frontend developer at Artbronze, Moscow

february 2022 - august 2022

Responsibilities:

- Web application development
- · Creating a UI of a web application using HTML5, CSS3, CSS Module based on Figma design layouts
- · Creating functional react components using react hooks
- Creating product tables
- Creating a personal account
- Working with Rest API, Axios
- Interaction with the team
- Fix bugs

TypeScript, React, Redux-Toolkit, Formik, React Router, Axios, HTML5, CSS3, Flex, Figma, yarn

Frontend developer (IT-Incubator, Moscow)

may 2021- march 2022

Technology stack: JavaScript(TypeScript), React, React-Toolkit, Redux-Form, Axios, Storybook, Postman, Jest, MUI, Axios, CSS3, Grid Layout, HTML5, CSS.

Stack

JavaScript	TS	Read	ct F	Redux	Redux-Toolkit		Redux-Thunk		Yarn	npm
Storybook	Postman		Git	Mater	Material UI		Grid Layout		CSS3	Jest